A Guide to the Amelia County (Va.) Judgments and Office Judgments, 1733-1913
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Amelia County (Va.) Judgments and Office Judgments, 1733-1913
The Library of Virginia
1138255-1138288, 1145808-1146050, 1160422, 1177430-1177445
146 cu. ft. (293 boxes)
Amelia County (Va.) Circuit Court
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restriction.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia in a transfer of court papers from Amelia County under the accession numbers 37995, 40724, 41507 and 43189.
Historical Information
Amelia County was formed from Prince George and Brunswick counties in 1734.
These judgments were created by the County Court, the Circuit Superior Court of Law and Chancery, and the Superior Court of Law.
Scope and Content
Amelia County (Va.) Judgments and Office Judgments, 1733-1913, contain civil cases in which justice was administered on the strictly formulated rules of common law. The majority of cases in this record series relate to matters of debt.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Additional Amelia County Court Records can be found on microfilm at the Library of Virginia. Consult "A Guide to Virginia County and City Records on Microfilm"
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Amelia County (Va.) Circuit Court.
Subjects:
Civil procedure--Virginia--Amelia County.; Debt--Virginia--Amelia County.; Public records--Virginia--Amelia County.
Geographical Names:
Amelia County (Va.)--History.
Genre and Form Terms:
Decisions--Virginia--Amelia County.; Judicial records--Virginia--Amelia County.; Local government records--Virginia--Amelia County.
Added Entry - Corporate Name:
Amelia County (Va.) Circuit Superior Court of Law and Chancery.; Amelia County (Va.) County Court.; Amelia County (Va.) Superior Court of Law.
Contents List
- Judgments 1733-1744 (Barcode 1138255)
- Various Judgment Series 1734-1799 (Barcode 1138288)
- Judgments 1741-1744 (Barcode 1160422)
- Judgments 1744-1748 (Barcode 1138256)
- Judgments 1748-1751 (Barcode 1138257)
- Judgments 1752-1753 (Barcode 1138258)
- Judgments 1754-1756 (Barcode 1138259)
- Various Judgment Series 1755-1796 (Barcode 1138287)
- Judgments 1756-1758 (Barcode 1138260)
- Judgments 1758-1761 (Barcode 1138261)
- Judgments 1762-1763 (Barcode 1138262)
- Judgments 1763-1764 (Barcode 1138263)
- Judgments 1764-1765 (Barcode 1138264)
- Judgments 1766-1768 (Barcode 1138265)
- Judgments 1768-1769 (Barcode 1138266)
- Judgments 1769-1772 (Barcode 1138267)
- Judgments 1773 (Barcode 1138268)
- Judgments 1774-1778 (Barcode 1138269)
- Judgments 1779-1784 (Barcode 1138270)
- Judgments 1782-1784 (Barcode 1138271)
- Judgments 1782-1785 (Barcode 1138272)
- Judgments 1785-1786 (Barcode 1138273)
- Judgments 1786 (Barcode 1138274)
- Judgments 1786-1787 (Barcode 1138275)
- Judgments 1787-1788 (Barcode 1138276)
- Judgments 1788-1789 (Barcode 1138277)
- Judgments 1789-1791 (Barcode 1138278)
- Judgments 1791-1792 (Barcode 1138279)
- Judgments 1793-1794 (Barcode 1138280)
- Judgments 1794-1795 (Barcode 1138281)
- Judgments 1795-1796 (Barcode 1138282)
- Judgments 1796 (Barcode 1138283)
- Judgments 1796-1798 (Barcode 1138284)
- Judgments 1798-1799 (Barcode 1138285)
- Judgments 1799 (Barcode 1138286)
- Various Judgment Series 1800-1805 (Barcode 1145833)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1800 (Barcode 1145808)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1800 (Barcode 1145809)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1800 (Barcode 1145810)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1801 (Barcode 1145811)
- Judgments 1801 (Barcode 1145812)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1801 (Barcode 1145813)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1801 (Barcode 1145814)
- Judgments--Memorandum of Suits 1801-1909 (broken series) (Barcode 1177443)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1802 (Barcode 1145815)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1802 (Barcode 1145816)
- Judgments 1802 (Barcode 1145817)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1802 (Barcode 1145818)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1803 (Barcode 1145819)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1803 (Barcode 1145820)
- Judgments 1803 (Barcode 1145821)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1803 (Barcode 1145822)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1803-1804 (Barcode 1145823)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1804 (Barcode 1145824)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1804 (Barcode 1145825)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1804 (Barcode 1145826)
- Judgments 1804 (Barcode 1145827)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1804-1805 (Barcode 1145828)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1805 (Barcode 1145829)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1805 (Barcode 1145830)
- Judgments 1805 (Barcode 1145831)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1805 (Barcode 1145832)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1806 (Barcode 1145834)
- Judgments 1806 (Barcode 1145835)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1806 (Barcode 1145836)
- Judgments 1806 (Barcode 1145837)
- Various Judgment Series 1806-1809 (Barcode 1145853)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1807 (Barcode 1145838)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1807 (Barcode 1145839)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1807 (Barcode 1145840)
- Judgments 1807 (Barcode 1145841)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1807 (Barcode 1145842)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1807 (Barcode 1145843)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1808 (Barcode 1145844)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1808 (Barcode 1145845)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1808 (Barcode 1145846)
- Judgments 1809 (Barcode 1145847)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1809 (Barcode 1145848)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1809 (Barcode 1145849)
- Judgments 1809 (Barcode 1145850)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1809 (Barcode 1145851)
- Office Judgments 1809 (Barcode 1145852)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1809-1810 (Barcode 1145854)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1810 (Barcode 1145855)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1810 (Barcode 1145856)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1810 (Barcode 1145857)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc 1810 (Barcode 1145858)
- Office Judgments, etc. 1810 (Barcode 1145859)
- Judgments 1811 (Barcode 1145860)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1811 (Barcode 1145861)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1811 (Barcode 1145862)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1811 (Barcode 1145863)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1811 (Barcode 1145864)
- Judgments 1812 (Barcode 1145865)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1812 (Barcode 1145866)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1812 (Barcode 1145867)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1812 (Barcode 1145868)
- Office Judgments and etc. 1812 (Barcode 1145869)
- Judgments 1813 (Barcode 1145870)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1813 (Barcode 1145871)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1813 (Barcode 1145872)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1813 (Barcode 1145873)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1813 (Barcode 1145874)
- Oversized Judgments 1813-1903 (broken series) (Barcode 1177445)
- Judgments 1814 (Barcode 1145875)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1814 (Barcode 1145876)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1814 (Barcode 1145877)
- Office Judgments and Judgments, etc. 1814 (Barcode 1145878)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1815 (Barcode 1145879)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1815 (Barcode 1145880)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1815 (Barcode 1145881)
- Various Judgment Series 1815 (Barcode 1145882)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1816 (Barcode 1145883)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1816 (Barcode 1145884)
- Office Judgments and Judgments, etc. 1816 (Barcode 1145885)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1817 (Barcode 1145886)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1817 (Barcode 1145887)
- Superior Ct of Law Judgments and OJ 1817 (Barcode 1145888)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1818 (Barcode 1145889)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1818 (Barcode 1145890)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1819 (Barcode 1145891)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1819 (Barcode 1145892)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1819 (Barcode 1145893)
- Superior Ct of Law Judgments, etc. 1819 (Barcode 1145894)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1820 (Barcode 1145895)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1820 (Barcode 1145896)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1820 (Barcode 1145897)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1820 (Barcode 1145898)
- Superior Ct of Law Judgments,etc. 1820 (Barcode 1145899)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1821 (Barcode 1145900)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1821 (Barcode 1145901)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1821 (Barcode 1145902)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1821 (Barcode 1145903)
- Superior Court of Law Judgments, et 1821 (Barcode 1145904)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1822 (Barcode 1145905)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1822 (Barcode 1145906)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1822 (Barcode 1145907)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1823 (Barcode 1145908)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1823 (Barcode 1145909)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1823 (Barcode 1145910)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1823 (Barcode 1145911)
- Judgments, etc. 1823 (Barcode 1145912)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1824 (Barcode 1145913)
- Judgments 1824 (Barcode 1145914)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1824 (Barcode 1145915)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1824 (Barcode 1145916)
- Office Judgments and etc. 1824 (Barcode 1145917)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1825 (Barcode 1145918)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1825 (Barcode 1145919)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1825 (Barcode 1145920)
- Office Judgments, etc. 1825 (Barcode 1145921)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1826 (Barcode 1145922)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1826 (Barcode 1145923)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1826 (Barcode 1145924)
- Office Judgments, etc. 1826 (Barcode 1145925)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1827 (Barcode 1145926)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1827 (Barcode 1145927)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1827 (Barcode 1145928)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1827 (Barcode 1145929)
- Various Judgment Series 1827 (Barcode 1145930)
- Judgments 1828 (Barcode 1145931)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1828 (Barcode 1145932)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1828 (Barcode 1145933)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1828 (Barcode 1145934)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1828 (Barcode 1145935)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1829 (Barcode 1145937)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1829 (Barcode 1145938)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1829 (Barcode 1145939)
- Office Judgments, etc. 1829 (Barcode 1145940)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1830 (Barcode 1145941)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1830 (Barcode 1145942)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1830 (Barcode 1145943)
- Various Judgment Series 1830 (Barcode 1145944)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1831 (Barcode 1145945)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1831 (Barcode 1145946)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1831 (Barcode 1145947)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1832 (Barcode 1145948)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1832 (Barcode 1145949)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1832 (Barcode 1145950)
- Various Judgment Series 1832 (Barcode 1145951)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1833 (Barcode 1145952)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1833 (Barcode 1145953)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1834 (Barcode 1145954)
- Various Judgment Series 1834 (Barcode 1145955)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1835 (Barcode 1145956)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1835 (Barcode 1145957)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1836 (Barcode 1145958)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1837 (Barcode 1145959)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1837 (Barcode 1145960)
- Office Judgments and Judgments, etc. 1837 (Barcode 1145961)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1838 (Barcode 1145962)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1838 (Barcode 1145963)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1838 (Barcode 1145964)
- Various Judgment Series 1838 (Barcode 1145965)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1839 (Barcode 1145966)
- Office Judgments and Judgments, etc. 1839 (Barcode 1145967)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1840 (Barcode 1145968)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1840 (Barcode 1145969)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1841 (Barcode 1145970)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1841 (Barcode 1145971)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1841 (Barcode 1145972)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1842 (Barcode 1145973)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1842 (Barcode 1145974)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1842 (Barcode 1145975)
- Judgments 1842 (Barcode 1145976)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1842 (Barcode 1145977)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1843 (Barcode 1145978)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1843 (Barcode 1145979)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1843 (Barcode 1145980)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1843 (Barcode 1145981)
- Various Judgment Series 1843 (Barcode 1145982)
- Judgments 1844 (Barcode 1145983)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1844 (Barcode 1145984)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1844 (Barcode 1145985)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1845 (Barcode 1145986)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1845 (Barcode 1145987)
- Office Judgments and Judgments,etc. 1845 (Barcode 1145988)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1846 (Barcode 1145989)
- Office Judgments and Judgments, etc. 1846 (Barcode 1145990)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1847 (Barcode 1145991)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1847 (Barcode 1145992)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1848 (Barcode 1145993)
- Office Judgments and Judgments,etc. 1848 (Barcode 1145994)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1849 (Barcode 1145995)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1849 (Barcode 1145996)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1849 (Barcode 1145997)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1850 (Barcode 1145998)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1850 (Barcode 1145999)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1851 (Barcode 1146000)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1852 (Barcode 1146001)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1853 (Barcode 1146002)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1854 (Barcode 1146003)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1854 (Barcode 1146004)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1855 (Barcode 1146005)
- Judgments, etc. 1855 (Barcode 1146006)
- Judgments and Office Judgments,etc. 1856 (Barcode 1146007)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1856 (Barcode 1146008)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1857 (Barcode 1146009)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1857 (Barcode 1146010)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1858 (Barcode 1146011)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1859 (Barcode 1146012)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1860 (Barcode 1146013)
- Office Judgments and Judgments, etc. 1860 (Barcode 1146014)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1861-1865 (Barcode 1146015)
- Judgments 1866 (Barcode 1146016)
- Office Judgments and Judgments 1866 (Barcode 1146017)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1867 (Barcode 1146018)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1867 (Barcode 1146019)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1868 (Barcode 1146020)
- Judgments 1868 (Barcode 1146021)
- Office Judgments and Judgments, etc. 1868 (Barcode 1146022)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1869 (Barcode 1146023)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1869 (Barcode 1146024)
- Office Judgments, etc. 1869 (Barcode 1146025)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1870 (Barcode 1146026)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1870 (Barcode 1146027)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1871 (Barcode 1146028)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1872 (Barcode 1146029)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1872 (Barcode 1146030)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1873 (Barcode 1146031)
- Office Judgments, etc. 1873 (Barcode 1146032)
- Judgments and Office Judgments 1874 (Barcode 1146033)
- Judgments, etc. 1874 (Barcode 1146034)
- Judgments, etc. 1875 (Barcode 1146035)
- Judgments, etc. 1876 (Barcode 1146036)
- Judgments, etc 1877 (Barcode 1146037)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1878 (Barcode 1146038)
- Judgments, etc. 1878 (Barcode 1146039)
- Judgments, etc. 1879 (Barcode 1146040)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1880 (Barcode 1146041)
- Judgments and Office Judgments, etc. 1881 (Barcode 1146042)
- Judgments, etc. 1882 (Barcode 1146043)
- Judgments, etc. 1883-1884 (Barcode 1146044)
- Judgments, etc. 1884 (Barcode 1146045)
- Judgments, etc. 1885 (Barcode 1146046)
- Judgments, etc. 1886 (Barcode 1146047)
- Judgments, etc. 1887 (Barcode 1146048)
- Judgments, etc. 1888 (Barcode 1146049)
- Judgments, etc. 1889 (Barcode 1146050)
- Judgments 1890 (Barcode 1177430)
- Judgments, etc. 1890 (Barcode 1177431)
- Judgments, etc. 1891-1892 (Barcode 1177432)
- Judgments, etc. 1893-1894 (Barcode 1177433)
- Judgments, etc. 1895-1896 (Barcode 1177434)
- Judgments, etc. 1897-1899 (see ext description) (Barcode 1177435)
- Judgments 1900 (Barcode 1177436)
- Judgments, etc. 1901 (Barcode 1177437)
- Judgments, etc. 1902-1904 (see ext description) (Barcode 1177438)
- Judgments, etc. 1905-1907 (see ext description) (Barcode 1177439)
- Judgments, etc. 1908-1909 (Barcode 1177440)
- Judgments 1910-1911 (Barcode 1177441)
- Judgments 1912-1913 (Barcode 1177442)
- Judgments Undated (Barcode 1177444)